Select Page

PRIVACY POLICY

**WARNING:** This service is monitored by the _**MyPropertyIDRegistry.com**_ security team. Abuse of this service is a violation of our [Terms](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/terms/) and [Privacy](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/privacy/) policies. We take the [Safety](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/safety/) of all of our users seriously and will not hesitate to involve law enforcement if there is evidence of abuse or harassment.

#### Privacy Policy

**COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**  
PaxAux, L.L.C. (collectively “PaxAux”) values the trust of our customers. PaxAux is committed to respecting the privacy of the visitors as we do business as (dba) MyPropertyIDRegistry.com (hereinafter collectively referred to as the “Site”). We are providing our Privacy Policy to you so you know the types of information we collect through this Site, and how the information is used.

**AGREEMENT TO CONSENT TO THE TERMS OF OUR POLICY**  
By using the MyPropertyIDRegistry.com Site, you consent to the information, collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**  
The following are examples of the ways MyPropertyIDRegistry.com collects information from you through the Site or otherwise:

* Provide us with comments, suggestions, or other input.
* Order MyPropertyIDRegistry.com products online.
* Provide us with information for the recovery of lost or stolen property.
* Conduct a transaction that requires us by law to collect such information.
* Use a social media service to communicate with MyPropertyIDRegistry.com customers, i.e. Facebook, Twitter or YouTube.

**TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
MyPropertyIDRegistry.com does not collect any personal information on the Site unless you voluntarily provide it to us. The following are examples of personal information collected by MyPropertyIDRegistry.com through the Site or otherwise:

* Your name.
* Your address.
* Your mobile number.
* Your home phone
* Your email address.
* Your credit/debit card number.

**INFORMATION NOT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE**  
We also collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

* We may collect information including, but not limited to, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone where a product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.

* Our web servers automatically collect usage information when you visit the Site. Site usage information is information about our visitors (unregistered users) and users that describes how the Site is used and navigated, including the number and frequency of visitors and users to each web page and the length of their stays. Site usage information also includes the domain names and/or corresponding IP addresses (a numerical identifier for a computer on the Internet) of those who visit the Site.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

**SECURITY**  
The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We will maintain appropriate safeguards to protect the security, integrity, and privacy of these servers and of your personally identifiable information. This includes encryption to protect credit and debit card numbers. Except as described herein, we will not use or intentionally disclose any personally identifiable information about you to any unaffiliated third parties without your consent.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
We may combine the personally identifiable information we collect from you when you use the Site with other information about you that is available to us, including survey information. We may use such information in several ways, including:

* To enable us to process and verify purchases, to provide you with the goods and services you have requested, and for the purposes disclosed when you provide the personally identifiable information.
* To send users email notifications of new features and topic-based news alerts if they have signed up for these announcements.
* To provide you with personalized content.
* To give the Site editors information that is useful for developing new features and services that meet users’ needs.
* To improve the content and navigation on the Site.
* To alert you about new products, services, and special offers.
* To contact you about your use of the Site or with regard to products and services.
* To meet the needs of your requests such as responding to emails.
* For internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve MyPropertyIDRegistry.com products, services, and customer communications.
* To monitor against theft.
* To comply with regulatory requirements.
* To assist law enforcement and to respond to subpoenas.

Finally, we may also use personally identifiable information to enforce our Website Terms and Conditions or share such information with (1) the issuer of a criminal or civil subpoena, (2) governmental authorities when legally required to do so, and (3) governmental authorities investigating a crime.

**YOUR ABILITY TO OPT OUT OR OPT IN**  
Opt Out. You can notify us that you do not wish to receive information about new products, services, and special offers by opting out at the time you enter your personally identifiable information on the Site. You may change your selections at any time by accessing your profile section on the Site after you have logged in.

Opt In. Several of the services we provide, including many of the email notifications and the surveys we conduct, are entirely voluntary. You will not receive such services unless you opt in, i.e., unless you expressly choose to receive these services.

**COOKIES**  
The Site, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies to help visitors and users move faster throughout the Site. When a visitor or user accesses the Site and takes advantage of certain features, we place several cookies on that user’s computer. A cookie is a string of information sent by a Site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer’s memory. This allows the Site to recognize you as you move through the Site. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

**REVIEW AND CORRECTION**  
You may review and update the personal information you provide us with as part of the registration process by accessing your profile after you login to the Site.

**SHARING INFORMATION**  
MyPropertyIDRegistry.com does not sell, rent, or otherwise provide personal information you provide through the Site or otherwise to outside marketers without prior consent, except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for MyPropertyIDRegistry.com to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

**OUR CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY**  
The Site and social media sites are not intended to feature information and services of interest to children 13 years and under. We do not collect information from anyone who we know is a child under the age of 13. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
For your convenience, the Site and social media sites contain links to other websites not maintained by MyPropertyIDRegistry.com. If you use these links, you will be directed away from the Site to the linked website. We do not assume responsibility for any of these websites, their content, or their privacy policies. If you choose to access any of the third party websites linked to the Site, you do so at your own risk and should review the privacy statements of these websites.

**CHANGES TO OUR POLICY**  
The Privacy Policy may change from time to time without notice, as provided by applicable law. Use of the Site shall constitute acceptance of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. Questions regarding the terms and conditions of MyPropertyIDRegistry.com privacy policies should be directed to it in the manner described in the “Contact Us” section.

**CONTACT US**  
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or MyPropertyIDRegistry privacy practices, you may use the “Contact Us” section of MyPropertyIDRegistry.com.

**POLICY SCOPE**  
This Privacy Policy applies to all current, former and guest information collected by or provided to MyPropertyIDRegistry.com. Any information collected will be maintained pursuant to MyPropertyIDRegistry.com Records Management Policy.

**WARNING:** This website is monitored by the **_MyPropertyID_** security team. Abuse of this service is a violation of our **[Terms](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/terms/)** and **[Privacy](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/privacy/)** policies. We take the **[Safety](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/safety)** of all of our users seriously and will not hesitate to involve law enforcement if there is evidence of abuse or harassment.

[SAFETY](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/safety) • [TERMS](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/terms/) • [PRIVACY](https://mypropertyidregistry.com/privacy/) Copyright © 2016-2024 PaxAux, L.L.C. All rights reserved.

* [](# "Chinese (Simplified)")
* [](# "Chinese (Traditional)")
* [](# "Myanmar (Burmese)")
